Guide to the National Education Association-Special Collections records, 1857-2015 NEA1007.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Projects, 1953-2000; Series 8; 90 Linear Feet
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Ohio-Meeting, 1977 August 16-17; Series 8 (Box 2749, Folder 7)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Ohio-Rossford Exempted Village [file 1/2], 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2750, Folder 1)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Ohio-Rossford Exempted Village [file 2/2], 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2750, Folder 2)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Ohio-Trimble Local, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2750, Folder 3)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Ohio-Troy, 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2750, Folder 4)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Avon Grove (Rural) [file 1/2], 1977-1979; Series 8 (Box 2750, Folder 5)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Avon Grove (Rural) [file 2/2], 1977-1979; Series 8 (Box 2750, Folder 6)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Bethlehem (Urban) [file 1/2], 1977-1979; Series 8 (Box 2750, Folder 7)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Bethlehem (Urban) [file 2/2], 1977-1979; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 1)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Butler area (Suburban), 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 2)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Churchill (Suburban), 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 3)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Dallas (Rural), 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 4)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania-Harrisburg (Urban), 1977; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 5)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Pennsylvania, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 6)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Phase I-General, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 7)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Phase II-General, 1978 February; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 8)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Proposal, 1976 Feburary 9; Series 8 (Box 2751, Folder 9)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Sharing Conference, 1978 May 20; Series 8 (Box 2752, Folder 1)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Sharing Conference-"Outcomes", 1977 May 14; Series 8 (Box 2752, Folder 2)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Bayview", 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2752, Folder 3)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Bayview", 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2752, Folder 4)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Bayview", 1978-1976; Series 8 (Box 2752, Folder 5)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Carbondale", 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2752, Folder 6)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Carbondale", 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2752, Folder 7)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Carbondale", 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2753, Folder 1)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Carbondale", 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2753, Folder 2)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-"Hope", 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2753, Folder 3)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Site Case Study-Watertown, 1979; Series 8 (Box 2753, Folder 4)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Sites Coordinators Handbook-Michigan Phase I Training Package, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2753, Folder 5)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Southland Linkage Case Study-Final, 1979; Series 8 (Box 2753, Folder 6)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Southland Site Case Study Document-Final, 1978 September; Series 8 (Box 2753, Folder 7)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Tennessee, 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 1)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Tennessee-Nashville Metro Area (Urban), 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 2)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Tennessee-Robertson County (Rural), 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 3)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Tennessee-University of Tennessee at Nashville, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 4)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Training-"Using R and D Products in Inservice Education" [file 1/2], 1978 March; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 5)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Training-"Using R and D Products in Inservice Education" [file 2/2], 1978 March; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 6)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Washington-Aberdeen (Suburban), 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 7)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Washington-Davenport (Rural), 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 8)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Wisconsin, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 9)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Wisconsin-Beloit/Turner (Rural), 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2754, Folder 10)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Wisconsin-Green Bay (Urban), 1977-1979; Series 8 (Box 2755, Folder 1)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Wisconsin-Little Chute (Rural), 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2755, Folder 2)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Wisconsin-Oak Creek (Suburban)-Site 764, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2755, Folder 3)
  - Project on Utilization of Inservice Education-Wyoming-Laramie County (Urban), 1977-1979; Series 8 (Box 2755, Folder 4)
  - Public Engagement Projects, 1997-1999; Series 8 (Box 4750, Folder 16)
  - Read Across America 2009 Resource Calendar, Series 8 (Box 4781, Folder 12)
  - Report of Task Force on Citizenship Education Curricula, 1972 June 21; Series 8 (Box 2755, Folder 5)
  - Report of The Task Force On Compulsory Education, 1972; Series 8 (Box 4906, Folder 9)
  - Report-Project 100, 1968-1978; Series 8 (Box 2755, Folder 6)
  - Salem-Keiser School District Classification Committee Training, 1999; Series 8 (Box 3178, Folder 5)
  - Satellite Project-Alaska, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 1)
  - Satellite Project-Alaska Experiment on ATS-1-USOE, 1968-1969; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 2)
  - Satellite Project-Appalachia Cumberland Meeting, 1976 December 17; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 3)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Evaluation Results Program No. 3`, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 4)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Evaluation Results Program No. 4, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 5)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska-Huntsville, AL Meeting, ca. 1975; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 6)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Intercom Comments on Program No. 1, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 7)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Intercom Program No. 3, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 8)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Project, 1971-1975; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 9)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Project Correspondence, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 10)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Project Evaluation Sheets Program 2, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 11)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Project-George Binder's Scripts, ca. 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 12)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Project Program One Support Material, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 13)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Project Program 2 Follow-Up Materials, ca. 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 14)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska Project-Questions Unanswered On-Air Program 3, ca. 1977; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 15)
  - Satellite Project-Appalaska-Skyline Inn, 1976 December 8; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 16)
  - Satellite Project-ATS-1, ca. 1976; Series 8 (Box 2756, Folder 17)
  - Satellite Project-ATS-6 Experiments, ca. 1975; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 1)
  - Satellite Project-ATS-6-Grayson, Larry Article, 1975; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 2)
    Grayson, Lawrence P.
  - Satellite Project-Attendance Sheets, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 3)
  - Satellite Project-Cable Chronological File, 1973-1976; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 4)
  - Satellite Project-Cable-New Jersey, 1973-1976; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 5)
  - Satellite Project-Cable TV-Educational Uses in Wisconsin, 1976; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 6)
  - Satellite Project-CTS Terminals, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 7)
  - Satellite Project-Final Evaluation Progam, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 8)
  - Satellite Project-Guam Earth Terminal, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 9)
  - Satellite Project-Implications of 1976 Copyright Law for Educators using Electronic Media, ca. 1976; Series 8 (Box 2757, Folder 10)
  - Satellite Project-Independent Broadcasting Authority (London), 1967-1972; Series 8 (Box 2758, Folder 1)
  - Satellite Project-Inner London Authority-ETV Project, 1968-1974; Series 8 (Box 2758, Folder 2)
  - Satellite Project-Manila Center for Educational TV, 1968; Series 8 (Box 2758, Folder 3)
  - Satellite Project-Manila-Regional Center for ITV for Southeat Asia, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2758, Folder 4)
  - Satellite Project-Names, Addresses, Miscellaneous, 1974-1976; Series 8 (Box 2758, Folder 5)
  - Satellite Project-NASA's Public Service Communications User Requirements Workshop; Tidewater Inn, 1976 October 17-19; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 1)
  - Satellite Project-Pan-Pacific Education Network Bystrom Proposal for a Feasibility Study May 1969 PEACESAT, 1969 May; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 2)
  - Satellite Project-Pan-Pacific Evaluation Sheets-Experiments, 1975-1976; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 3)
  - Satellite Project-Persons Who Had a Role in the Project, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 4)
  - Satellite Project-Phillipines-TV Projects, 1966-1970; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 5)
  - Satellite Project-Professional Excellence Project-Hawaii State Teachers Association, Undated; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 6)
  - Satellite Project-Public Interest Satellite Association, 1976; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 7)
  - Satellite Project-Public Interest Satellite Assn Meeting; Meeting of Experimenters; PISA's Board of Advisors, 1976 October 1-2; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 8)
  - Satellite Project-Publicity Appalaska Project, 1975-1977; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 9)
  - Satellite Project-PSSC Conference, 1976 December 8-10; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 10)
  - Satellite Project-Program 3 Support Materials, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 11)
  - Satellite Project-Rural Supplemental Educational Center, Stamford NY, Rexmere Park, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2759, Folder 12)
  - Satellite Project-The RFD System, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2760, Folder 1)
  - Satellite Project-Tony Brown Speech [Audio & Transcript], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2760, Folder 2)
  - Satellite Project-Transportable Assisted Professional Diagnosis & Help for Handicapped Children, Undated; Series 8 (Box 2760, Folder 3)
  - Satellite Project-Trinidad & Tobago, 1966; Series 8 (Box 2760, Folder 4)
  - Satellite Project-Trinidad & Tobago-NAEB Study, 1966; Series 8 (Box 2760, Folder 5)
  - Satellite Project-Washington County Closed Circuit Television, ca. 1956; Series 8 (Box 2760, Folder 6)
  - School Violence Project [1/2], 1976; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 1)
  - School Violence Project [2/2], 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 2)
  - School Violence Project AEA-NEA Title: Positive Expectation for Student Behavior and Achievement; to: Javetta Richardson, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 3)
  - School Violence Project: Application for Funding, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 4)
  - School Violence Project: Background Info/School Violence, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 5)
  - School Violence Project Causey, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 6)
  - School Violence Project: Center for Human Services, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 7)
  - School Violence Project Colorado Springs Teachers Assn Proposals, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 8)
  - School Violence Project East Providence Education Assn Proposals, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 9)
  - School Violence Project: Evaluation Reports, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 10)
  - School Violence Project: Form Originals, 1976; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 11)
  - School Violence Project: Grant Activity Report, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 12)
  - School Violence Project: Grant Application, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2761, Folder 13)
  - School Violence Project: Grants, Documentation for Accrual Money, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2762, Folder 1)
  - School Violence Project: Hawaii State Teachers Assn Proposals, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2762, Folder 2)
  - School Violence Project Information, 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2762, Folder 3)
  - School Violence Project IPD Paper on State by State Inservice Teacher Program 1974 [1/2], Series 8 (Box 2762, Folder 4)
  - School Violence Project IPD Paper on State by State Inservice Teacher Program 1974 [2/2], Series 8 (Box 2762, Folder 5)
  - School Violence Project IPD Pre-RA Conference Longer School Day/Year [1/2], 1983; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 1)
  - School Violence Project IPD Pre-RA Conference Longer School Day/Year [2/2], 1983; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 2)
  - School Violence Project IPD Teacher's Conference HE Sponsors, 1974; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 3)
  - School Violence Project Law Suit for School Safety, 1979-1980; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 4)
  - School Violence Project Letters-Violence Grants, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 5)
  - School Violence Project Little Rock Arkansas Eleanor Coleman 4120 W. Markham St. Suite 202 Little Rock Arkansas 72205, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 6)
  - School Violence Project Little Rock C.T.A., 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 7)
  - School Violence Project Little Rock Classroom Teachers Assn Project, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 8)
  - School Violence Project Little Rock Classroom Teachers Assn: Application Form, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 9)
  - School Violence Project Massachusetts Teachers Assn Proposals, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 10)
  - School Violence Project Money Paid to Affiliates for Grants, 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2763, Folder 11)
  - School Violence Project NEA HR Conference, 1980; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 1)
  - School Violence Project Outgoing Memo & Correspondence, Septemeber 1979; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 2)
  - School Violence Project Packet, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 3)
  - School Violence Project PAT (Portland), 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 4)
  - School Violence Project Portsmouth Education Assn Proposals, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 5)
  - School Violence Project PEA/Citywide Committee to Study Discipline Problems, 1975-1977; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 6)
  - School Violence Project Response to John's Request for Info for Uniserv Directions, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 7)
  - School Violence Project Safe Schools Program, 1977-1979; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 8)
  - School Violence Project Summary of Violence Program, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 9)
  - School Violence Project Stress Management Course, Undated; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 10)
  - School Violence Project Teacher Opinion Poll Info, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 11)
  - School Violence Project Violence in Schools to State Pres., State Educ., and State HR contacts, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 12)
  - School Violence Project Washington Education Assn, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 13)
  - School Violence Project Washington Education Association School Violence Program, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 14)
  - School Violence Project-Washington Education Project, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 2764, Folder 15)
  - State Education Association-Arizona Education Association: Annual Reports, 1995-1999; Series 8 (Box 2765, Folder 1)
  - State Education Association-Colorado Education Association: Annual Reports [1/2], 1997-1999; Series 8 (Box 2765, Folder 2)
  - State Education Association-Colorado Education Association: Annual Reports [2/2], 1996-1999; Series 8 (Box 2766, Folder 1)
  - State Education Association-Kansas Education Association: Annual Reports [1/2], 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 2766, Folder 2)
  - State Education Association-Kansas Education Association: Annual Reports [2/2], 1995-1999; Series 8 (Box 2767, Folder 1)
  - State Education Association-Nebraska Education Association: Annual Reports, 1994-1999; Series 8 (Box 2767, Folder 2)
  - State Education Association-New Mexico Education Association: Annual Reports, 1996-1999; Series 8 (Box 2767, Folder 3)
  - State Education Association-Oklahoma Education Association: Annual Reports [1/2], 1986-1999; Series 8 (Box 2768, Folder 1)
  - State Education Association-Oklahoma Education Association: Annual Reports [2/2], 1990-1998; Series 8 (Box 2768, Folder 2)
  - Status of the American Schoolteacher Paperwork [1/2], 1961-2001; Series 8 (Box 3303, Folder 7)
  - Status of the American Schoolteacher Paperwork [2/2], 1961-2001; Series 8 (Box 3303, Folder 8)
  - A Summary of the Report of the NEA Project on Instruction Schools for the Sixties, undated; series 8 (Box 4378, Folder 10)
  - Supervisory & Administrative Service Project, Undated; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 1)
  - Teacher Centers & Advisory Work, 1978; Series 8 (Box 4904, Folder 1)
  - Task Force-Bilingual/Bi-cultural Education-Papers & Reprints, 1974-1975; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 2)
  - Task Force-Collective Bargaining, 1968-1975; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 3)
  - Task Force-Compulsory Education-Report, 1972; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 4)
  - Task Force-Corporal Punishment-Report, 1972; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 5)
  - Task Force-Displaced School Personnel, Desegregation-Report, December 1965; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 6)
  - Task Force-Drug Education-Report-"An Awakening", 1972; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 7)
  - Task Force-Future Flight Manpower Study-Education, February 1964; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 8)
  - Task Force-Higher Education-Report, June 1968; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 9)
  - Task Force-Local Association Structure-Documents, Reports, Minutes, 1968-1969; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 10)
  - Task Force-Memoranda- Departmental Relations, 1967-1983; Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 11)
  - Task Force-NEA Departmental Relations-Papers, Series 8 (Box 2769, Folder 12)
  - Task Force on Organizing and Servicing Substitutes, Part-Time and Paraprofessional Personnel, ca. 1974; Series 8 (Box 2770, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on Puerto Rico: Loose Items in Box, Correspondence & Reports, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2770, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on Puerto Rico: Loose Items in Box, Press Release & Spanish Language Material, 1979; Series 8 (Box 2770, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on Puerto Rico: Loose Items in Box, Task Force Reports & Observations, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2770, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on Puerto Rico: News & Press Releases, 1979; Series 8 (Box 2770, Folder 6)
  - Task Force on Puerto Rico: Tragedia en las Escuelas, 1979; Series 8 (Box 2770, Folder 7)
  - Task Force on Puerto Rico: Tragedy in the Schools-Working Copy, ca. 1979; Series 8 (Box 2770, Folder 8)
  - Task Force on Testing, Testimony from Testing Industry, National Association et al, 1972-1973; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 1)
  - Task Force-Paraprofessionals-Report, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 2)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Action Programs, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 3)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Agendas, January-June 1970; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 4)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Chicago, Illinois, December 27-30, 1970, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 5)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Correspondence, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 6)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Correspondence on Rights Statement, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 7)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Correspondence with Task Force members, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 8)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-General Correspondence, 1970-1972; Series 8 (Box 2771, Folder 9)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-General File-Contacts, Notes, Things to do, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2772, Folder 1)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-GRIP Workshops, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2772, Folder 2)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Interoffice Correspondence, 1969-1972; Series 8 (Box 2772, Folder 3)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Mailings, January-September 1970; Series 8 (Box 2772, Folder 4)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-New Orleans, September 17-20, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2772, Folder 5)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Position Statement Drafts, April-June 1970; Series 8 (Box 2772, Folder 6)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Position Statement Draft-Final Copy, April-June 1970; Series 8 (Box 2772, Folder 7)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Proposed Programs, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 1)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Revised Edition of Working Paper, April-July 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 2)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-"Student Rights and Responsibilities", 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 3)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Temporary File-To NY for discussion with Jerry (George) Gumeson, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 4)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcription-Conference-New York City, Columbia College, January 30, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 5)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcription-Conference-New York City, 105 Madison Avenue, January 28, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 6)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcription-Conference-New York City, Seek University Center, January 29, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 7)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcription-Conference-New York City, Statler Hilton [1/3], January 28, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 8)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcription-Conference-New York City, Statler Hilton [2/3], January 30, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 9)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcription-Conference-New York City-Statler Hilton [3/3], Januray 31, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 10)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Denver, March-April 1970; Series 8 (Box 2773, Folder 12)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Denver-Hilton Hotel [1/4], April 22, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 1)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Denver-Hilton Hotel [2/4], April 22, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 2)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Denver-Hilton Hotel [3/4], April 22, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 3)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Denver-Hilton Hotel [4/4], April 22, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 4)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Speaker-Liethen, Michael, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 5)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Speaker-Van Maes, Robert, March 26, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 6)
  - Task Force-Student Involvement-Transcriptions-Speaker-TEPS Commission, March 24, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 7)
  - Task Force-Testing-Report, 1972-1975; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 8)
  - Task Force to Study Campaign Costs-Mailing to Taks Force Members, August 22, 1984; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 9)
  - Task Force to Study Campaign Costs-Bernie Freitag comments (Candidate survey), 1984; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 10)
  - Task Force to Study Campaign Costs-Candidate's Campaign Expenditures, 1978, 1980-1984; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 11)
  - Task Force to Study Campaign Costs-Candidate Survey Raw Data, 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 12)
  - Task Force to Study Campaign Costs-Candidate Survey Results, 1984; Series 8 (Box 2774, Folder 13)